Marta Esparcia López

Bachelor's Degree in Chemical Engineering.

Master's Degree in Energy Engineering

Date of birth: 08/06/1999 Nationality: Spanish Phone: +34 676271233

Email: marta.esparcia.lopez@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/marta-esparcia-lópez-68b466212

Chemical Engineer with a strong work ethic and motivation, interested in energies, particularly renewable energy and the transformation of the future energy landscape.

WORK	EXPER	<u>IENCE</u>
-------------	--------------	--------------

September 2023	Engineer in technical feasibility study.
_	Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingeniería y Diseño Industrial. Universidad Politécnica de Madrid in collaboration
February 2024	with European Engineering Learning Innovation and Science Alliance.
Februaryo 2022 – May 2022	Research assistant. Instituto de Catálisis y Petroleoquímica (ICP). Consejo Superior de Investigaciones Científicas (CSIC).

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

September 2022 – February 2024	Master's Degree in Energy Engineering. Specialization in Renewable Energies. Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingenieros Industriales (ETSII). Universidad Politécnica de Madrid (UPM).
Septiembre 2017 – Julio 2022	Bachelor's Degree in Chemical Engineering. Escuela Técnica Superior de Ingeniería y Diseño Industrial (ETSIDI). Universidad Politécnica de Madrid (UPM).
September 2015 – June 2017	High School. Colegio Claret (Madrid).

EXPERIENCE

November 2021	Teacher of the Arduino and Chemical Sensors Course organized by the student section of ISA ETSIDI and the student association of the robotics club CREA ETSIDI.	
April 2021 – November 2021	Participant as a mentee in the "Mentoring Project" taught by Manuel Zafra Palacios and organized by the student section of the International Society of Automation (ISA) of ETSIDI.	
September 2021 (50 hours)	Course "How can Biomass Contribute to Sustainability and Use of Renewables" taught by Prof. Dr. Axel Blokesch, University of Applied Sciences (Frankfurt).	
March 2021 – May 2021 (40 hours)	"Emerson" Course on Industrial Process Regulation and Control taught by Emerson and organized by the student section of ISA ETSIDI.	

KNOWLEDGE

Programming:		Languages:
	ļ	Spanish (Native)
MS Office (high level)	LIDER-CALENDER (HULC)	English (C1)
AutoCAD	Aspen Hysys	French (B1-B2)
MatLab	C++	
WAsP	EcosimPro	Multiple times I have had experiences abroad. In 2015 I did an
PVsyst	Step 7	exchange in Paris to improve my level of French. In addition, in 2015
Thermoflow	Promax	and 2016 I did a linguistic immersion in English, in Ireland and England.

Additional Information:

- Driving License type B.
- Active member of the ISA student section at ETSIDI.
- Active member of the Robotics, Electronics, and Automation Club at ETSIDI, UPM.
- Nationally certified lifeguard. Spanish Royal Federation of Lifesaving and Lifeguarding. Since 2016.
- Flute studies (2nd professional level). Amaniel Professional Music Conservatory (2015 2018).

SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Communication
- Generosity and tolerance
- Adaptation to the environment
- Organization
- Ability to learn and work
- Iniciative

